asiatoday.com 2006-12-31

# Asian Manufacturers, Asian Suppliers - AsianNet / Global B2B - Asia, China, Taiwan, Trade Directory, Marketplace, Chinese Products, Taiwan Products, China Exporters, Taiwan Exporters

This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the AsianNet.com Site. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use Agreement between you and AsianNet.com which by use of this Site you agree to accept. 

**The Information We Collect**

Registration Information: At the time you register to become a Member of the Site, you will be asked to complete an application form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business ("Registration Information.") 

Publishing Information: If you upload or submit any information to AsianNet.com to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Profile, Product Listing, Trade Leads, News Listing, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information ("Publishing Information"). 

**How We May Use Information**

General: We use your Collected Information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site's content, layout and service specifically for you. We may use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our Users. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users. We may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message. 

Registration Information: We may use your Registration Information to provide services that you request or to contact you regarding additional services about which AsianNet.com determines that you might be interested. Specifically, we may use your email address, mailing address, phone number or fax number to contact you regarding notices, surveys, product alerts, new service or product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our Site. We may generate reports and analysis based on the Registration Information for internal analysis, monitoring and marketing decisions. 

Publishing Information: All of your Publishing Information will be publicly available on the Site and therefore accessible by any internet user. Any Publishing Information that you disclose to AsianNet.com becomes public information and you relinquish any proprietary rights (including but not limited to the rights of confidentiality and copyrights) in such information. You should exercise caution when deciding to include personal or proprietary information in the Publishing Information that you submit to us. 

Top

**Disclosure of Information**

We reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of AsianNet.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority. 

If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of Service Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to AsianNet or others. 

Top

**Minors**

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site and so we carry out the same Privacy Policy for individuals of all ages. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information. 

Top

**Security Measures**

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information. 

As a Member, your Registration Information and Publishing Information can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., Member ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. 

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

Top

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact AsianNet.com in writing (at the address set out in the Notice provision of the Terms of Use Agreement) and specifically request that AsianNet.com return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information in AsianNet.com's possession. This Privacy Policy was last amended on June 6, 2006. 

Top

**Correcting Your Information**

You can access, view and edit your Member Information and Publishing Information through your Account with AsianNet.com. To update or correct such information, please [click here](http://bestproducts.asiannet.com/manager/).
